Washingtoniana Slide Collection P026 P026
Test
- Series 1: Historic Image Collection
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1965 April (Item 335)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1954 April 17 (Item 336)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 337)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1958 April (Item 338)
      View of the Jefferson Memorial and Washington Monument through the cherry trees (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1957 April 11 (Item 339)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 340)
      View of the Jefferson Memorial through the cherry trees and hand rail (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 341)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 342)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 343)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1949 April 1 (Item 344)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1949 April 1 (Item 345)
      View of the Jefferson Memorial at dusk (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 346)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 347)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1949 April 1 (Item 348)
      View of the Jefferson Memorial with boat in Tidal Basin (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 349)
      View of the Jefferson Memorial with cherry trees (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1949 April 1 (Item 350)
      View of the Jefferson Memorial with cherry trees along tidal basin (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1957 April 11 (Item 351)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1958 April (Item 352)
      View of people walking under cherry trees with Jefferson Memorial in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 353)
    - Cherry Blossom (Tidal Basin), 1957 April 11 (Item 354)
      View of Jefferson Memorial from bridge over Tidal Basin (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Monuments (Constitution Avenue between 3rd and 4th Streets NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 355)
      Memorial for Major General George Meade by Charles Grafly (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Monuments (Constitution Avenue and 17th Street NW), 1960 April (Item 356)
      Second Division Memorial by James Earle Fraser (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Monuments (Ellipse, State Place and 17th Street NW), 1967 January (Item 357)
      The First Division "Big Red One" Memorial by Daniel Chester French (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Corcoran Gallery (500 17th Street, NW), 1970 June (Item 358)
      Modern Art sculpture outside Corcoran Gallery of Art (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Corcoran Gallery (500 17th Street, NW), 1967 January (Item 359)
      Exterior of the Corcoran Gallery of Art (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Renwick Gallery (17th Street and Pennsylvania Avenue), 1960 April (Item 360)
      Exterior of old Corcoran Gallery of Art, now the Smithsonian Institution Renwick Gallery of Art (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Blair-Lee House (1651-1653 Pennsylvania Avenue, NW), 1967 January (Item 361)
      Exterior of the Blair-Lee House and Renwick Gallery (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Blair-Lee House (1651-1653 Pennsylvania Avenue, NW), 1960 April (Item 362)
      Exterior of the Blair-Lee House (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Decatur House (Lafayette Square), 1967 January (Item 363)
      Exterior of the Stephen Decatur House (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Decatur House (Lafayette Square), 1967 January (Item 364)
    - Garden (20th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1964 June (Item 365)
      View of garden, note locates it at the Federal Reserve Board Building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Federal Reserve (20th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 366)
      Exterior of the Federal Reserve Board Building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Federal Reserve (20th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1964 June (Item 367)
    - Federal Reserve (20th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1964 June (Item 368)
      Fountain outside the Federal Reserve Board Building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (Lafayette Park), 1972 May (Item 369)
      Houses along side Lafayette Park (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Fountain (Lafayette Park), 1970 June (Item 370)
      Fountain in Lafayette Park with people sitting around it (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parks (Lafayette Park), 1963 October (Item 371)
      A bench in Lafayette Park with Saint John's Episcopal Church in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - White House (Lafayette Park), 1963 October (Item 372)
      The White House from Lafayette Park with Andrew Jackson statue in foreground (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (901 Newton Street, NE), 1971 April (Item 373)
      The Brooks Mansion (Bellair) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (18th Street and New York Avenue NW), 1963 October (Item 374)
      View of the Octagon House and New York Avenue (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Houses (1801 F Street, NW), 1963 October (Item 375)
      View of the DACOR-Bacon (Francis Low) House (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Houses (1801 F Street, NW), 1963 October (Item 376)
    - Pan American Building (17th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1970 May (Item 377)
      View of Aztec statue in the Aztec garden at Pan American Union Building (Organization of American States building) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pan American Building (17th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1967 May (Item 378)
      Flowers in the Aztec garden at Pan American Union Building (Organization of American States building) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pan American Building (17th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1967 May (Item 379)
      View of the flowers and fountain in the Aztec garden at Pan American Union Building (Organization of American States building) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pan American Building (17th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1967 May (Item 380)
      View of bust in the Aztec garden at Pan American Union Building (Organization of American States building) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pan American Building (17th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1964 June (Item 381)
      Flowering tree in the Aztec garden at Pan American Union Building (Organization of American States building) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pan American Building (17th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1964 June (Item 382)
      View of the Aztec garden at Pan American Union Building (Organization of American States building) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pan American Building (17th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1960 April (Item 383)
      Exterior view, from the driveway, of the Pan American Union Building (Organization of American States building) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Pan American Building (17th Street and Constitution Avenue, NW), 1960 April (Item 384)
      Exterior view, from 17th Street, Pan American Union Building (Organization of American States building) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - American Red Cross (17th and E Street, NW), 1963 October (Item 385)
      Exterior view of the American Red Cross building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - American Red Cross (17th and E Street, NW), 1967 January (Item 386)
      Exterior view of the American Red Cross building in the snow (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Continental Hall (1776 D Street, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 387)
      Exterior view of the Memorial Continental Hall (Daughters of the American Revolution) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Continental Hall (1776 D Street, NW), 1960 April (Item 388)
    - Memorials (E and 18th Streets NW), 1963 April (Item 389)
      Statue of General Símon Bolívar by Felix W de Weldon (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Federal Buildings (1849 C Street, NW), 1963 October (Item 390)
      Exterior view of the Department of the Interior building (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Federal Buildings (1849 C Street, NW), 1960 April (Item 391)
      Exterior view of the Department of the Interior building and the statue of General Símon Bolívar by Felix W de Weldon (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 October (Item 392)
      US Navy band welcoming home the FWS Geronimo (Note on Geronimo found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 October (Item 393)
      FWS Geronimo sails into port at the US Navy Yard (Note on Geronimo found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 November (Item 394)
      View of main mast of the FWS Geronimo (Note on Geronimo found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 October (Item 395)
      Group of men on the bridge of the FWS Geronimo (Note on Geronimo found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 October (Item 396)
      View of the FWS Geronimo docked at the US Navy Yard (Note on Geronimo found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 August (Item 397)
      View of the bridge of the FWS Geronimo (Note on Geronimo found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 October (Item 398)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 October (Item 399)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 October (Item 400)
      Rockwell, Wilson, Dr. Thomas Austin, Donald McKernan, and Dr. J. L. McHugh on dock next to FWS Geronimo (Note on Geronimo found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 401)
      Dr. Thomas Austin and Donald McKernanon dock next to FWS Geronimo (Note on Geronimo found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 August (Item 402)
      FWS Albatross II docked at the US Navy Yard (Note on Albatross found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 August (Item 403)
      On board the FWS Albatross II, docked at the US Navy Yard (Note on Albatross found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 August (Item 404)
      View of US Navy Yard docks, with two ships docked, and people looking at exhibits on shore (Note on Geronimo found in control file) (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 October (Item 405)
      View of people standing on the dock at the US Navy Yard (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 406)
      View of outdoor exhibits including captured canons and "freedom's bell" (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 June (Item 407)
      View of the docks at US Navy Yard with shipped docked (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 June (Item 408)
      People touring ship docked at US Navy Yard (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1963 August (Item 409)
      Navy Oceanographic Vessel docked a US Navy Yard (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 410)
      Sailors rowing boat near USS State of Maine (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 411)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 412)
      Navigation bowie at the US Navy Yard (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 413)
      View of outdoor exhibits including captured canons (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 414)
      View of the Navy Yard showing a canon and docked ship (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 415)
      View of outdoor exhibits including a tank, canon and torpedo (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 416)
      Canon taken from the deck of the USS Maine (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 417)
      Captured Nazi submarine at US Navy Yard (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 418)
      View of outdoor exhibits including a tank and canon (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Navy Yard (Anacostia River), 1965 May (Item 419)
      View of captured canon at US Navy Yard (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1951 June 17 (Item 420)
      People walking near grotto at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1971 June (Item 421)
      Detail of roses at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), Ca. 1950 (Item 422)
      View of an altar at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), Ca. 1950 (Item 423)
      Exterior view of building (Blessed Sacrament Chapel?) at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1970 May (Item 424)
      Detail of mountain laurel at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1970 May (Item 425)
      Statue of Saint Christopher by John Joseph Earley at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1964 August (Item 426)
      Garden and statue of Godfrey Schilling at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1966 June (Item 427)
      Statue of Saint Bernadette by Mary E Lynch at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1970 May (Item 428)
      Statue of Saint Francis by Porfirio Rosignoli at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1970 May (Item 429)
      People walking through the garden at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1970 May (Item 430)
      Lourdes Grotto at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1970 May (Item 431)
      Man walking through garden at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1966 June (Item 432)
      Woman standing in portico at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1966 June (Item 433)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1964 August (Item 434)
      Exterior view of main church and Saint Christopher statue at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1964 June (Item 435)
      View of a Rosary Portico in the garden at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1962 September (Box 436)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1949 May 29 (Item 437)
      Woman and child in the garden at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1970 May (Item 438)
      Man taking pictures in the garden at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1949 May 29 (Item 439)
      People in the garden at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), Ca. 1950 (Item 440)
      Exterior view of the main church at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), Ca. 1950 (Item 441)
      Detail of roses in the garden at Mount Saint Sepulcher, Franciscan Monastery and Commissariat of the Holy Land in America (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), 1971 June (Item 442)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), Ca. 1950 (Item 443)
    - Franciscan Monastery (1400 Quincy Street NE), Ca. 1950 (Item 444)
    - Memorials (Constitution Avenue and 1st Street, NW), 1964 June (Item 445)
      Robert A. Taft Memorial and Carillon (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Monuments (National Mall), 1958 May (Item 446)
      View of the Washington Monument (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Monuments (National Mall), Ca. 1953 (Item 447)
      View of the Washington Monument and the Reflecting Pool (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Monuments (National Mall), 1951 June 17 (Item 448)
    - Monuments (National Mall), Ca. 1950 (Item 449)
      View of the Washington Monument and the US Capitol from the Lincoln Memorial (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Monuments (National Mall), 1949 May 12 (Item 450)
      View of Lincoln Memorial (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Monuments (National Mall), 1964 September (Item 451)
      Interior of Lincoln Memorial, sculpture by Daniel Chester French (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Monuments (National Mall), 1964 September (Item 452)
    - Monuments (National Mall), 1964 September (Item 453)
    - Monuments (National Mall), Ca. 1950 (Item 454)
      Lincoln Memorial and the Reflecting Pool (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1957 April 11 (Item 455)
      Washington Monument through the cherry tree blossoms (Photographer: Unknown)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1957 April 11 (Item 456)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1957 April 11 (Item 457)
      Jefferson Memorial through the cherry tree blossoms (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1958 April (Item 458)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 459)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 460)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 461)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 462)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1949 April 1 (Item 463)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 464)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 465)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 466)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 467)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1958 April (Item 468)
      Washington Monument and Jefferson Memorial through the cherry tree blossoms (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1964 April (Item 469)
      Japanese Lantern through the cherry tree blossoms (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1964 April (Item 470)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1964 April (Item 471)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 472)
      Japanese Lantern, with Geisha, through the cherry tree blossoms (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1965 April (Item 473)
      Japanese Pagoda through the cherry tree blossoms (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1957 April 11 (Item 474)
      People walking under the cherry tree blossoms (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), 1964 April (Item 475)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Cherry Blossoms (Tidal Basin), Ca. 1950 (Item 476)
      Cherry tree blossoms along Tidal Basin (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Church, 1975 August (Item 477)
      Unknown Church (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Church, 1975 August (Item 478)
    - Parade (Takoma Park), Ca. 1950 (Item 479)
      4th of July parade float with boy scouts (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade (Takoma Park), Ca. 1950 (Item 480)
      4th of July parade float sponsored by Takoma Park Chamber of Commerce (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade (Takoma Park), Ca. 1950 (Item 481)
      4th of July parade US Navy fire engine (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade (Takoma Park), Ca. 1950 (Item 482)
      Old car at 4th of July parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade (Takoma Park), Ca. 1950 (Item 483)
      Old car in 4th of July parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade (Takoma Park), Ca. 1950 (Item 484)
      Evening Star soap box derby float in 4th of July parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Soap Box Derby (Pennsylvania Avenue), Ca. 1950 (Item 485)
      Car racing in the Evening Star Soap Box Derby (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, 1954 May 18 (Item 486)
      Color guard from High School band during safety parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, 1954 May 18 (Item 487)
    - Parade, 1955 August 15 (Item 488)
      Girl performing during parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, Ca. 1950 (Item 489)
      Color guard during parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, 1955 August 15 (Item 490)
      Drumline from band during parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, 1955 August 15 (Item 491)
      Marching band during parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, Ca. 1950 (Item 492)
      Color Guard from high school band during parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, Ca. 1950 (Item 493)
      Girls performing during parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, 1955 August 15 (Item 494)
      High school band during parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, Ca. 1955 (Item 495)
  - Historic Image Collection (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Parade, 1955 August 15 (Item 496)
    - Streets (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1949 May 29 (Item 497)
      View of Pennsylvania Avenue with parade arch over it, US Capitol in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Streets (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1949 May 30 (Item 498)
    - Streets (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1963 October (Item 499)
      Crowded Pennsylvania Avenue after parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Streets (Pennsylvania Avenue), Ca. 1950 (Item 500)
      Men marching down Pennsylvania Avenue during parade, US Capitol in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, Ca. 1950 (Item 501)
    - Parade, 1950 July (Item 502)
      Old car during Masonic/Shriner parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, Ca. 1950 (Item 503)
      Two old cars during Masonic/Shriner parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade, Ca. 1950 (Item 504)
      Clown in Masonic/Shriner parade (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade (Pennsylvania Avenue), Ca. 1950 (Item 505)
      Marchers, in costume, in Masonic/Shriner parade - US Capitol in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1950 July (Item 506)
    - Parade (Pennsylvania Avenue), 1950 July (Item 507)
      Marchers, in costume caring rifles, in Masonic/Shriner parade - US Capitol in background (Photographer: Unknown)
    - Parade (Pennsylvania Avenue), Ca. 1950 (Item 508)
    - Parade (F and 10th Streets, NW), Ca. 1950 (Item 509)